Mike cernovich how are meet you fin nice
to meet you too thanks for coming in I
think I actually trolled your show I'm
sure you did you you and the I forget
the rapper's name did a problematic like
rap or something on cultural
appropriation did I trigger you
definitely didn't I thought it was kind
of funny you thought that the video was
funny or trolling me was funny both oh
yeah success yeah um so what is a I
use it just to mean beta week I use it
very I wouldn't consider really why not
no I would call you beta I would say
you're beta so I'm not all the way at CU
beta is just a non-aggressive maybe a
little bit passive of a man yeah and
with this kind of hairstyle you have
more respect for a cuck or a beta than a
normie like at least that's something no
normi is great normi just like they
don't get it for example I don't do
satire anymore why not Norm's not AR so
good at it well it's a little 5 years
later do do you hate the left definitely
not that's why we're having a
conversation I usually say no I say I've
turned down The Daily Show I've turned
down everybody and I appreciate you
being here I always say no to TV because
all you people want to do is edit things
out of context I give you my word we
would never edit you out of context like
that that's not the kind of show we do
here what's uh what's the most cuck
thing you've ever done I had sex with
Bill Clinton with the strap on e oh
yes all right what do you hope to
accomplish longterm I like the idea of
sucking Hitler
penis it's on
theist okay uh do people hate you I
deserve a lot of the hate that I get
there are things that I've said or done
I've been mean to people gratuitously
and I wish I hadn't done that so when
people are mean to me I just view that
as karma yeah what's the soundtrack of
the alt-right I like house
music we love
it a lot of people ask me all the time
people ask me what think about Hillary
she's beautiful intelligent C me as I
told your show TR your show hilan
dialectic your
[Music]
show I love trolls hillian
dialectic yeah
[Laughter]
yeah thanks for coming in Mike I
appreciate it thanks for
[Applause]
coming